betrush.com 2018-04-15

# Betrush.com :: Terms and Conditions | Disclaimer | Privacy Policy

### Terms and Conditions

1\. This is agreement between Betrush.com (the site), the visitors and users of services provided by Betrush.com.  
2\. The visitor confirms that he is at least 18 years old and his country of residence allows visiting gambling related sites.  
3\. Betrush.com does not offer bookmaking or gambling of any form. All content of the site is provided solely for information and entertainment purposes.  
4\. All materials contained on the site are intellectual property of Betrush.com and their respective authors. Copying any content without permission is strictly forbidden.  
5\. Users of the service located on betrush.com/premium cannot share active content to 3rd parties in whatever way, including redistribution or replicating of picks or providing access to the site to 3rd parties. User accounts are limited to one person only. Breaching this rule will lead to immediate termination of the user's account.  
6\. Any payments made to Betrush.com are not refundable.  
7\. Upon registration the users of Betrush agree to receive communication by the site at the provided email address and can reject any further messages by request or using the "Unsubscribe" option provided in the communication.  
8\. Betrush.com cannot be held responsible for any loss or damage as consequence of decisions based on information, betting advices or 3rd party links provided on this site. The visitor is warned to act and follow betting advices exclusively at his own discretion and risk.  
9\. The special T&C (rules) for using any of the different services provided by Betrush.com are published / linked to on the respective pages requiring registration to these services and represent undivided part of these terms. 

### Play responsibly

Betrush is committed to responsible gambling. Any information appearing on the site is not meant in any way to be a source of professional advice or recommendation to bet or gamble. The visitor is warned that gambling involves high psychological and financial risks and he acts exclusively at his own discretion and responsibility. If experiencing gambling problems, seeking help from a professional body such as Gamblers Anonymous or Gambleaware is highly advised.

### Disclaimer

Betrush.com cannot guarantee the correctness of information contained within its pages, or of information obtained from 3rd parties. Betrush.com cannot be held responsible for any loss or damage as consequence of decisions based on information, betting advices or 3rd party links provided on this site. 

In a region where betting or gambling is not permitted this site should be used for informational purposes only, and not with a view to betting or gambling via a 3rd party website, including those linked to by Betrush.com, where betting or gambling is facilitated. It is the individual's responsibility to ensure that any activity with a 3rd party which facilitates the placement of bets does not breach the laws relating to betting or gambling of the country or state where the individual is based. Under no circumstances will Betrush.com be liable for any breach of state or country law that may occur as a result of an individual's usage of this website, or of any other 3rd party website. 

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how Betrush.com uses and protects any information that you give when using this site.

Betrush.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Collection of data:

We do not require and collect any personal data except email addresses of users registered to some of our services. The administrator may also receive general information that is contained in the server log files, such as IP addresses of the visitors accessing Betrush.com. We require this information to provide a better service and stay in contact with the users interacting with the site.

Security:

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to any 3rd parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

### Cookies

By accessing, continuing to use or navigating throughout the site you accept that we will use certain browser cookies. The cookies used by Betrush.com do not interfere your privacy. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your device's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. 

What cookies we do use:

Session cookies exist while you are logged in. They are needed for users to interact with the site ;  
3rd party cookies (such as Google Analytics)- used for analyzing the traffic data and interests of our visitors while being on the site so we can provide you with better experience at Betrush.com;

Cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose if to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can modify your browser settings to decline them. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. If you would like to know more about cookies visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

### Links to other websites

Betrush.com contains links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
